http://www.stuartwinesco.com.au/privacy-policy.aspx

close
Subtotal:
Privacy Policy
Stuart Wines’ is committed to supporting the 'National Privacy Principles for the Fair Handling of Personal Information' which set clear standards for the collection, access, storage and use of personal information which we obtain as part of our business operations.
Our respect for our customers' right to privacy of their personal information is paramount. We have policies and procedures to ensure that all personal information, no matter how or where it is obtained, is handled sensitively, securely, and in accordance with the National Privacy Principles.
This Privacy Policy sets out: matters of which you should be aware regarding information we may collect about you, our policies on the management of personal information, and generally, what sort of information we hold, for what purposes, and how we collect, hold, use and disclose that information.
What personal information do we collect and store?
So that we can provide services to you, we may ask for personal details such as your name, address, telephone number or email address. Privacy law requires us to collect personal information about you only from you if it is reasonable and practical to do so.
Stuart Wines’ takes measures to ensure your personal information is protected from unauthorised access, loss, misuse, disclosure or alteration. We also take measures to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information when it is no longer required. The types of measures we take vary with the type of information, and how it is collected and stored.
Generally, you have no obligation to provide any information requested by us. If you choose to withhold requested information however, we may not be able to provide you with the goods and services that depend on the collection of that information, particularly if the collection of that information is required by law.
How is personal information used?
The personal information that we ask for is generally used to provide goods or services to you. For example, for a credit card transaction we need your card number.
We may also use your personal information in other ways to provide you with superior service. This may include using your personal information to advise you of new products and services. You have the right to tell us that you do not want us to send information to you other than for the main purpose for which we have collected your personal details.
Where possible, we try to ensure that our disclosure of information to other organisations (for example market researchers, and others with whom we have commercial arrangements) is in a way which does not personally identify individuals.
Security
We take security seriously, and have taken steps to ensure your personal information is secure. When you place orders online, we use a secure server that encrypts all your personal information before it is sent to us to prevent unauthorised access to your information. We do not store credit card details on our website.
Access to your personal information
We will provide you with access to any of your personal information we hold (except in the limited circumstances recognised by privacy law).
If you need to update your information (eg. if you change your address), please contact the relevant part of Stuart Wines’ to which you supplied that information so we can make the change.
